Historical Photograph Collection: Glass-Plate Negatives Series, 1880-1920: Preliminary Finding Aid AC317
University Archives
- Athletics, 1881-1938; 51 boxes
  - Track and Field, 1912-1920; 13 boxes
    - Finish of half mile run in intercollgiates, 1920, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 380
      Plate number: 875
    - Start of 2-mile run in intercollgiates, 1920, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 381
      Plate number: 876
    - Fourth lap of 2-mile run intercollgiates, 1920, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 382
      Plate number: 877
    - Seventh lap of the 2-mile run in intercollgiates, 1920, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 383
      Plate number: 878
    - Finish of 2-mile run in intercollgiates, 1920, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 384
      Plate number: 879
    - First lap of 2-mile run in intercollegiates, 1920, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 385
      Plate number: 880
    - Semifinal heat of low hurdles in intercollegiate meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 386
      Plate number: 881
    - Final of low hurdles in intercollegiate meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 387
      Plate number: 882
    - Earl Thomson, world champion hurdler, Undated; 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 388
      Plate number: 883
    - Jack Merchant, star California hammer thrower, Undated; 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 389
      Plate number: 884
    - 1912 Rupert Thomas 100 yard dash, 4th heat, Ohio Field, 1 box (Box 54)
      Broken
    - Hi Blauvelt running on board track, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1052
      Plate number: 1058
    - Ray Sanger running on board track, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1053
      Plate number: 1059
    - George Trowbridge hurdling, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1054
      Plate number: 1060
    - John Barrett, Stewart, and Hocaday starting a sprint in track practice, Undated; 1 box (Box 58)
      Original sleeve No. 1146
      Plate number: 1125
    - Erdman and Trowbridge hurdling in track practice, Undated; 1 box (Box 58)
      Original sleeve No. 1147
      Plate number: 1126
    - Athletics, Caledonian games, W.M. Davy highjumping, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1231
    - Athletics, Caledonian games, H.J. Richardson broadjumping, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1232
    - Athletics, Caledonian games, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1233
    - Athletics, track, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1250
    - Athletics, track, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1251
  - Water Polo, 1915-1919; 2 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture the Princeton University Water Polo team.
    - Water polo game, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1055
      Plate number: 1061
    - Water polo game, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1056
      Plate number: 1062
    - Athletics, water polo intercollegiate champions, 1915?, circa 1915; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1252
    - Athletics, water polo, 1917 winner of class series, circa 1917; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1253
  - Wrestling, 1917-1922; 4 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture the Princeton University Wrestling team.
    - Varsity wrestling team in winter of 1917, 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 156
      Plate number: 688
    - Sibley's wrestling bout in Yale meet, 1918, 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 157
      Plate number: 689
    - C.C. Carpenter 1921 of wrestling team 1920, 1920-1921; 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 158
      Plate number: 690
    - J.S. Jacobs of 1920 wrestling team, 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 159
      Plate number: 691
    - W.S. Red 1920 of 1920 wrestling team, 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 160
      Plate number: 692
    - F.H. McKnight, 1922 of 1920 wrestling team, 1920-1922; 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 161
      Plate number: 693
    - Washington's birthday wrestling meet, 1918, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1057
      Plate number: 1063
    - Chuck Carpenter in wrestling bout in Yale meet, 1918, 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1097
      Plate number: 1096
    - Athletics, wrestling, Gus Peterson coaching Ned Hamilton '17 and J.S. Baker '15, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1254
- Buildings and Grounds, 1811-1944; 71 boxes
  Glass plates within this series show Princeton University and Princeton town buildings and grounds. Also included are architectural renderings of University buildings.
  - Alexander Hall, 1916-1919; 4 boxes
    This subseries shows views of Alexander Hall.
    - Alexander, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 395-396
    - Alexaner, south and west facades, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 397
    - Alexander, south facade, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 398
    - Alexander, north facade, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 399
    - Cloister of Alexander Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 410
      Plate number: 905
    - Alexander Hall, 1919, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 411
      Plate number: 906
    - Alexander Hall, 1916, 1 box (Box 58)
      Original sleeve No. 1120
      Plate number: 1118
    - Alexander Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 111)
      Plate number: 372
  - Blair Hall, 1916-1918; 6 boxes
    This subseries shows views of Blair Hall.
    - Blair Hall, steps and tower, top of Witherspoon at right, Undated; 1 box (Box 5)
      Plate number: 106
    - Blair, looking west, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 185
    - Blair, tower and steps, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 186
    - Blair Hall, with part of Witherspoon, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 187
    - Blair Hall, from north, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 188
    - Blair, tower and steps, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 189
    - Blair Hall with tower and steps, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 190
    - Blair, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 400
    - Blair, arch and people on steps, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 401
    - Blair, tower and steps, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 402
    - Blair Hall arch, 1918, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 396
      Plate number: 891
    - Blair Hall from below arch, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 431
      Plate number: 926
    - Blair Hall arch, 1916, 1 box (Box 58)
      Original sleeve No. 1122
      Plate number: 1120
  - Boathouse, 1915-1918; 4 boxes
    This subseries consists of images of the Princeton University boathouse.
    - Boat house, Undated; 2 boxes (Box 5, Box 6)
      Plate number: 107-109
    - Boathouse, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 231
    - Boathouse, crews launching sculls, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 403
  - Building Interiors, 1915-1918; 14 boxes
    This subseries consists of interior images of Princeton University buildings.
    - Classroom, McCosh?, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 120
    - Palmer Lab? interior, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 143-144
    - Princeton University Press interior, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 156
    - Dining Hall interior, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 200
    - Unknown interior with ducts, Undated; 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 320
    - Dining Hall interior, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 433
    - Service entrance to the dining halls, 1918, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 395
      Plate number: 890
    - Kitchen court of the commons, 1918, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 397
      Plate number: 892
    - Corner of Willard Wattle's room, #92, Undated; 1 box (Box 54)
      Original sleeve No. 540
      Plate number: 1012
    - The kitchen of the University seen from 1D Hamilton Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1069
      Plate number: 1075
    - Interiors, classrooms and labs, Civil Engineering lab with students mixing concrete, Undated; 1 box (Box 70)
      Plate number: 1346
    - Interiors, classrooms and labs, Civil Engineering lab with students pouring concrete, Undated; 1 box (Box 70)
      Plate number: 1347
    - Interiors, classrooms and labs, Physical Geography Class with Prof. Libbey, Guyot 10, Undated; 1 box (Box 70)
      Plate number: 1348
    - Interiors, classrooms and labs, Physical Geography Class with Prof. Libbey, Guyot 10, Undated; 1 box (Box 70)
      Plate number: 1349
    - Interiors, classrooms and labs, Guyot Hall Lab, alumni visit with students working, Undated; 1 box (Box 70)
      Plate number: 1350
    - Interiors, classrooms and labs, 50 McCosh, German exam, Undated; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Interiors, classrooms and labs, 50 McCosh, German exam, Undated; 1 box (Box 70)
      Plate number: 1352
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, W.M. Phelps, 3A Hamilton, Undated; 1 box (Box 70)
      Plate number: 1353
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, 3B Hamilton, McNichol-Drorbaugh Room, Undated; 1 box (Box 70)
      Plate number: 1354
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, 3B Hamilton, McNichol-Drorbaugh Room, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
      Plate number: 1355
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, Cohu Room, 154 Little, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
      Plate number: 1356
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, Cohus' Room, 154 Little, 2 brothers class of 1917, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
      Plate number: 1357
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, H.W. Cohu in front of fireplace, 154 Little, 1915?, circa 1915; 1 box (Box 71)
      Plate number: 1358
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, Edward Durell reading in front of fireplace, 7 S. Reunion, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
      Plate number: 1359
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, Edward Durell dreaming in front of fireplace, 7 S. Reunion, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
      Plate number: 1360
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, Jim Healey's Room, 38 University Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, unidentified student's room, circa 1915; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Interiors, dormitory rooms, unidentified, undated; Potter, Mary Elizabeth Thomas; 1 item (Box 73)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      This glass plate negative is broken.
      Potter, Mary Elizabeth Thomas
    - Interiors, miscellaneous, water polo in Brokaw Pool, Pennsylvania vs. Princeton, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Interiors, miscellaneous, Graduate College common room, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Interiors, miscellaneous, Graduate College common room, people listening to a lecture, circa 1915; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Interiors, miscellaneous, gym, William Long doing handstand on ring, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Interiors, miscellaneous, Halsted Observatory telescope, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Interiors, miscellaneous, Princetonian Office with candidates, Undated; 1 box (Box 71)
    - Unknown interior (powerhouse switchboard), Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
    - Unknown Interior (ducts), Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
    - Unknown Interior (laboratory? powerhouse? workshop?), Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
    - Classroom, Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
    - Unknown interior (ducts), Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
    - Interior, bust on wall shelf, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Large interior wreath on display, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Fireplace, emblem over mantel, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Interior, arched doorway and top of stairs, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
    - Church interior from choir, stained glass, Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
      7x5
    - Library Interior, bust and early telephone, Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
    - Probable library interior; room with bookshelves and long table, undated; 1 item (Box 113)
  - Building Exteriors, 1916-1926; 6 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries include an assortment of various exterior shots of Princetion University buildings.
    - Stone building (unknown) street, Undated; 1 box (Box 92)
    - Stone building (unknown) street, Undated; 1 box (Box 92)
    - Entrance exterior - towers, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Building exterior, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Exterior buildings, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Building, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Great buildings, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
    - Building exterior, full shot of tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
    - Building exterior, some damage, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
    - Building exterior, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
    - Building, exterior tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 98)
    - Building exterior, Undated; 1 box (Box 98)
    - Tower Building exterior, Undated; 1 box (Box 98)
    - Exterior long building, Undated; 1 box (Box 99)
    - Exterior buildings Towers, Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
    - Exterior, house on left, Monument Rd., Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
    - Exterior building, fence with one man standing, Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
    - Exterior building, Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
    - Exterior building, tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
    - Exterior building, planetarium, Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
    - Mill house? exterior, Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
    - Building exterior, Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
    - Stone building with gables and ivy, undated; 1 item (Box 113)
  - Campbell Hall, 1918; 5 boxes
    This subseries shows views of Campbell Hall.
    - Campbell Hall, early construction photo, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 110
    - View through Campbell Arch toward Blair, Undated; 1 box (Box 16)
      Plate number: 316
    - Campbell, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 407
    - Entrance to Campbell Hall, 1918, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 399
      Plate number: 894
    - Tigers on Campbell Hall arch, Undated; 1 box (Box 52)
      Original sleeve No. 478
      Plate number: 980
  - Campus Views, 1890-1914; 10 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture views of the Princeton University campus.
    - Sesquicentennial Arch, the one at the intersection of Stickton and Nassau Street, western front, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 152
    - Sesquicentennial Arch, the one at the intersection of Stickton and Nassau Street, eastern front, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 153
    - View accross front campus to Green School of Science, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 173
    - View from west, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 175
    - View from south, Blair at end of walk, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 176
    - View looking west, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 177
    - View looking south, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 178
    - View from top east wing of McCosh, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 179
    - Views, east, Nassau, old chapel, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 181
    - View, west, Reunion, Stanhope, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 182
    - View with Blair, Little, and Witherspoon, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 230
    - View up Chambers Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 229
    - View from Nassau Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 319
    - View from west, the wash day photo, Undated; 1 box (Box 14)
      Plate number: 298-299
    - View from golf course to north, circa 1914; 2 boxes (Box 16, Box 17)
      Plate number: 317-318
    - Birds Eye View, 1890's, from the west, circa 1890; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate in a smaller envalope
      Plate number: 497
    - View, Brokaw Memorial at left, DOD at right, from south, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 593
    - View, toward gate, between Blair and Little, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 594
    - View, walk with Brokaw Arch at end, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 595
    - View, Brown and DOD, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 596
    - View, Witherspoon, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 597
    - View, toward Foulke, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 598
    - View, Alexander and Blair, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 599
    - View, Blair and Witherspoon, from west, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 600
    - View, Edwards and Clio, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 601
    - View, Pyne Library Arch to Blair?, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 602
    - View, Alexander, Blair, Bonner-Marquand gym, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 603
    - View, Alexander, Campbell, Halsted Observatory, Holder, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 604
    - View, Pyne Library, Marquand Chapel spire, Murray-Dodge, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 605
    - View, Murray-Dodge, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 606
    - View, toward Marquand Chapel, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 607-610
    - View, toward Nassau Street, Reunion, Stanhope, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 611
    - View, front campus, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 612
    - View, up walk to Blair, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
      Plate number: 613-614
    - View from below Blair arch showing Blair, Little and Witherspoon Halls, Undated; 1 box (Box 48)
      Original sleeve No. 420
      Plate number: 915
  - Cannon Green, 1916-1919; 3 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Cannon Green.
    - Cannon Green, Pyne Library, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 194-195
    - Cannon Green, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 196
    - Cannon, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 409
    - Cannon Green with Whig and Clio, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 410
  - The Casino, 1916-1919; 2 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show the Princeton University Casino, an early clubhouse used for social gatherings. The Casino was constructed in 1895 and burned down on January 8, 1924.
    - Casino. being moved from second site to third, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 111
    - Casino on second site, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 112
    - Casino, probably on its first site, 1895-1901, Undated; 1 box (Box 15)
      Plate number: 304
  - Chancellor Green, 1916-1919; 6 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show views of Chancellor Green.
    - Chancellor Green reading room looking towards circulation desk in Pyne, Undated; 1 box (Box 15)
      Plate number: 305
    - Chancellor Green and Pyne Library, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 414
    - Chancellor Green interior, toward circulation desk, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 415
    - Corner of Chancellor Green library, fall of 1919, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 409. (Pic. cover)
      Plate number: 904
    - Buildings and grounds, Chancellor Green door in winter, Jan. 1916, 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1255
    - Class reunion, Chancellor Green, Undated; 2 boxes (Box 19, Box 20)
      Plate number: 342-347, 349
  - Chapel, 1907-1928; 12 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show views of the Princeton University Chapel and its predecessor, the Marquand Chapel.
    - Chapel, late construction, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 114
    - Chapel, 1928, part of J.C. Green School of Science on left, 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 115
    - Chapel, rendering west facade with cloister at right, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 116
    - Marquand Chapel, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 139
    - Mather Sundial, dedication taken from McCosh window with crowd in foreground, class of '77 LAJ, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 140
    - Mather Sundial, just erected, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 141
    - Marquand Chapel, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 180
    - Chapel, interior, construction at pulpit, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 198
    - Chapel, west facade with people, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 199
    - Marquand Chapel after the fire, with sundial behind center arch, Undated; 1 box (Box 16)
      Plate number: 310
    - Mather Sundial, 1907; 1 box (Box 16)
      Plate number: 311
    - Marquand Chapel, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 382, 385
    - Marquand Chapel, Murray Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 383
    - Marquand Chapel, exterior, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 384
    - Marquand Chapel and Library, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 386
    - Chapel, north and west facades, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 416
    - Chapel, west facade, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 417
    - Chapel, main door, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 418
    - Chapel, interior toward west, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 419
    - Chapel interior, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 420
    - Chapel from choir, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 421
    - Christian student with Gailey, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 422
    - Marquand Chapel interior, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 478
    - Mather Sundial, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 479
    - Mather sun dial, Undated; 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1060
      Plate number: 1066
    - Memorial tablet at entrance to old chapel, Undated; 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1067
      Plate number: 1073
    - Buildings and grounds, Marquand Chapel from Prospect Gateway, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1260
    - Indoor chapel stained glass, Undated; 1 box (Box 99)
    - Outdoor building, chapel?, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
  - Chemistry Lab (Aaron Burr Hall), 1899-1923; 2 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show the Princeton University Chemistry Lab, once housed in Aaron Burr Hall.
    - Chemistry lab, Aaron Burr Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 117
    - Chemistry lab with man working, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 118
    - Aaron Burr Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 392-393
  - Cuyler Hall, 1899-1923; 3 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Cuyler Hall.
    - Cuyler, west facade, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 121
    - Cuyler, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 430
    - Cuyler Hall from tower of Patton Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1063
      Plate number: 1069
  - Eating Clubs, 1899-1923; 12 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show the Princeton University Eating Clubs.
    - Tiger Inn, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 154-155
    - Tiger Inn Fireplace, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 233
    - Tiger growling, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 232
    - Cannon Club, 1899-1911; 1 box (Box 12)
      Plate number: 278
    - Cap & Gown, original building, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 411
    - Cap & Gown, present building, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 412
    - Campus Clubs, early house, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 408
    - Colonial Club, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 425
    - Colonial Club, undated; 1 item (Box 113)
    - Colonial, present building, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 426
    - Dial Club, original Cap & Gown building, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 431
    - Cottage Club, old building on Prospect Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 427
    - Cottage Club, new building from south, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 428
    - Cottage, present building, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 429
    - Ivy Club, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 460
    - Elm Club, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 437
    - Key and Seal, old building, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 465
    - Tiger Inn, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 522
    - Quadrangle, old building, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)